All right.
That one broke too?
I'd rather buy a new one...
This one's still good if I can fix it.
We don't need a new one.
How's school going?
Okay.
You've at least been going, right? You'll pass this semester?
Of course.
That's great.
You're always working so hard.
Good morning, Kobato!
Good morning-
Kobato tripped again!
Stop tripping!
Are you okay, Kobato?
Oh man...
Why do you keep tripping over your own feet?
Owie...
Thank you.
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... A kind person.
Fujimoto!
I'll help out! Let me do it!
Fine, whatever.
Okay!
Um, Fujimoto?
Mind if I ask you something?
Fujimoto?
Shut up and get back to work. I don't have time right now for your gum-flapping.
Okay...
What is it, anyway?
Er?
What did you want to ask me?
Well, um...
It's about that strange phone call earlier.
Why can't I tell Miss Sayaka about it?
You just can't.
Why can't I?
If you can't keep quiet, you should just go away.
She'll be worried if she hears about it.
That's why.
Miss Sayaka will be worried?
Are you here to help out, or just to get in the way?
What's wrong, Kobato?
I got Fujimoto mad again.
He's mad?
Yeah.
I always get in his way.
You should apologize. Let's go do it together.
I'm sure he's just mad because he's worried about you.
Really?
Yeah! Cheer up!
Mama always says she's mad because she wants me to be a good boy.
That's right. I'll apologize and ask to help again.
Huh? He's not here.
What's this?
Oh, that has to be Fujimoto's report.
Report?
I think it's due today.
Can you bring it to him?
Me?
I think he really needs it.
I'll bring it to him!
Don't get too excited.
I'm always getting in his way. I want to show him I can do something right for once.
Fujimoto's university is this way, right?
Didn't you ask directions!?
Yeah!
But wait, what's a university?
What, you don't even know that!?
Well, at this point, I shouldn't be too surprised at your lack of common sense.
A university's a place where you study complicated things.
Study?
Yeah.
Maybe there's something he wants to do, or a career he aspires to.
Something he wants to do?
Wow, there's so many people!
Of course, it's a university. They always have this many.
I wonder how many of Yomogi you could fit in here?
You can't even compare them!
Just hurry up and find him.
Okay, Ioryogi!
Um...
Oh, I'm sorry!
Er, um, huh?
Don't get yourself lost!
I can't find Fujimoto.
You're just wandering the halls!
I'll try my best! ... Huh?
It's Fujimoto!
What are you spacing out for?
That's right!  I have to give it to him!
Don't fall over again!
Sorry, are you okay?
Yeah...
I'm sorry too!
Nah, I'm fine.
That's a cute stuffed animal you have.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks!
Are you a friend of Kiyokazu's?
No!
No... Not really a friend, just, uh...
Something like that?
Yeah, I guess.
Me too.
You're...?
I'm Domoto Takashi. And you are-?
Pleased to meet you! I'm Hanato Kobato!
I came to bring Fujimoto something he'd forgotten...
Fujimoto!
Huh? He was just here.
He must've run away.
I ticked him off earlier.
Again?
"Again"?
He gets angry so fast!
But it's because I always screw up so much...
I still think he gets angry too often, though!
But it's always my fault, not his...
I see, you're the one from Yomogi Nursery.
Yeah! I help out there.
All right, Kobato, let's go look for Kiyokazu.
Are you sure you want to look for Fujimoto?
What, you think I'll get in the way?
No, no, you'll be a great help!
That's great.
Hm, he's probably in Philosophy of Law right now.
It's okay, I think he'll be here all day.
He's finally taking a day off from work.
Really?
Yeah, exams are coming up.
He always seems so busy.
Yeah, he always talks big about taking extra classes, but then he puts his work first.
Oh well, that's just how he is.
Domoto! Give me a hand!
What's up?
Can you help me out?
I don't even know where to start on Professor Hayakawa's report!
He assigned it for next week out of nowhere!
Fine, fine, okay.
All right!
Thanks, Domoto!
I'll help out, but you need to do the real work.
Fine, whatever!
Thanks!
Oh man...
Anyway, let's get going.
Fujimoto? I haven't seen him. Try the library maybe?
Thanks.
If you see him, tell him I was looking for him.
No way!
He's so standoffish it's scary.
No he isn't.
Anyway, sorry, but I can't.
Is everyone that scared of Fujimoto?
It's because he's always so unsociable and angry-looking.
You too, Domoto?
You said he was mad at you earlier...
Well, he had reason to be.
He's always been the type that hates relying on people.
And I gave him advice on his future.
I ran my mouth, even though I knew he didn't like it.
Why?
Well, I can't just let him go on like this...
Miss Sayaka!
What is it?
Everyone's waiting! Let's play!
Sorry, I can't. Fujimoto and Kobato are both gone today.
I'll have to pass.
Fine then.
Wait just a little bit, okay?
Miss Sayaka! There's someone here!
Hi!
Chiho! Chise!
And Chitose! What is it?
We made macaroons with Mama, so we came to share them!
Oh my!
Let's eat!
They're so tasty and crisp!
Where are Kiyokazu and Kobato?
They both went to school today.
Kobato too?
Fujimoto? He left a while back.
Really? Thanks. I'll keep looking.
Hey, Domoto.
Yeah?
Professor Tomita likes you, right?
Mind giving him a talk? I'm screwed if I flunk this year.
Have you tried going to him yourself?
Nah, I'm too afraid.
You're on good terms with him, if you could just get things started...
Fine, I'll talk with him.
Really? You're a lifesaver!
But you've got to go to him after that.
Everyone relies on Domoto, don't they, Ioryogi?
Sure, sure. Thanks!
Kobato!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I don't mind.
Mind if I stop on the way?
No problem!
Even if you say so, his attendance is a bit-
He understands that.
Please, isn't there something you can do, Professor Tomita?
Fine. If you're that insistent...
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're great, Domoto.
Great? How?
So many people rely on you, and you're able to help them.
Really?
Yeah!
I want to help people out, but I'm never quite good enough...
You're wonderful, Domoto.
Thanks... I guess.
Huh?
Nah, never mind. Let's go.
Okay!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I lost!
Okay, Chiho's it.
Everyone go hide!
One... Two...
So that's why she went to the university.
She was so excited.
That's really like her.
Hey, Sayaka, take a look at this.
Yukari!
Chise?
Which one are you?
Caught you, Yukari!
You were Chiho?
This is the person that said they'd be willing to discuss a loan.
This is an accountant I know.
And this is...
Sorry, Chitose.
Do you understand, Sayaka?
I'm not helping you out of pity.
My daughters and I all attended Yomogi, so we want to protect it.
So you don't need to apologize.
Thanks.
There you are!
What's wrong with you!?
You're just slacking off. I don't feel like helping you.
If you didn't want me to lend a hand, you could've just said so!
Fine, I don't want to.
Fine!
You were no help at all!
What are you doing here?
Fujimoto, you're a meanie!
What is it this time?
Why do you have to talk down to people like that?
You're just trying to make them mad!
If I don't they'll just sponge off me more.
Maybe they had a reason.
I don't care!
They should do their own work.
I brought the report you forgot!
Kobato...
I went way too far...
Kobato.
Domoto...
Oh! You helped me find Fujimoto and I didn't even say thanks.
I'm sorry.
Have a seat.
How long have you known Kiyokazu?
Well... Since spring of this year.
Really?
Why?
I'm a bit jealous.
Of the two of you.
Us? Why?
I've known him a lot longer,
but I can't be as direct with him as you can.
I must have made him angry...
I was so rude...
No, that's not it. You were right.
I just can't bring myself to be honest with him.
Sorry, I'm asking too much.
But you're wonderful in so many ways.
You're so kind...
I'm not kind at all.
But you're kind enough to listen to everyone, and help them out.
I'm just not good at saying no.
They'd be better off if I turned them down like Kiyokazu does.
You're just slacking off. I don't feel like helping you.
Kiyokazu's strong. He's not afraid of people hating him.
People avoid him because they feel overpowered by that strength.
I'm jealous of it.
You're jealous of his strength?
Yeah.
I don't know about Fujimoto,
but being feared is lonely.
Being hated hurts.
Everyone you met today looked so happy when they heard you'd help.
But that's just-
Domoto!
What's wrong with not wanting to be hated?
What's wrong with wanting to be liked?
What's wrong with wanting to help people?
What's wrong with wanting to do something for people in trouble?
I don't know quite how to say it, but...
Domoto, you're a good person.
Thanks.
Huh?
You're such an strange kid.
Really? Did I say something weird?
Ioryogi always gets mad and says I don't know anything...
Ioryogi?
Yeah!
Ioryogi is a stuffed animal, but he can talk.
But even though he talks I'm not supposed to talk to him!
Hey...
Is that Ioryogi there?
Yes!
Domoto!
They're---
See you later.
Yeah! Thanks!
No, thank you.
See you!
Later!
Why do I have more candy?
Probably because you recognized that metrosexual guy's kindness.
Metrosexual? You mean Domoto?
Who else would I mean?
Just recognizing it got me more candy?
He was worried about what people thought of him.
Really?
Metrosexuals have their own issues, I guess.
By the way, Dobato. About this afternoon...
Yes?
What the hell were you doing telling him about me!?
But I didn't talk to you, just like you said!
You can't go around telling people that stuffed animals talk!
Sorry!
30 points, Kobato!
Come on!
Didn't I already tell you thanks?
Fujimoto's always like this.
He's so awkward. He was trying to thank you deeply.
Thank me?
Is Mr. Kiyokazu done being mad with you, Kobato?
He's not scary! He's kind!
He's kind! When I lost my key, he found it!
He made me a take-tonbo!
He found me a cicada shell!
He's not bad.
Fujimoto is a strange person.
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... A kitten's lullabye.
Next episode